Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.02.24 14:07:53
不让你搭车了 你自己走路上班吧
明白了 你在精神上被强奸了 我们可以继续了吗? 下面来的可是猛料
你怎么能给这样的事找到理由的? 你闯进Stacy的心理医生的办公室...
借了个钥匙
...而且偷了她的档案!
没有!我复印了
Mark是 我证明
"孤僻 被动的好斗 不愿交流 就好像他在嫉妒我能走路"
我不想听这个
盘子堆在水池里 坐便器的垫子掀着
同时 她情不自禁的想...
我看不懂这个 是她困扰于一个叫Grey Horse的? 还是我?
这上面说她认为你是个讨厌的蠢货
那是个宠物的名字
重点是这个
他们没有爱爱?
医生允许了 但是没点火
她很沮丧 所以她在想法子修理我
文书 开会 管我的病人的闲事
好极了 你现在有了想要的证据 ...
把这些个人治疗文件拿给Cuddy 证明Stacy失去控制了
你忽视我?
在找我的报纸 很有效率吧?
这儿呢!
Wilson医生 这位是我的跟踪者
你的等待室真糟
我不会治你的
什么 因为你是个玻璃?
呃...我们不是... 呃...那个那个
他是不大愿意
嗯 我们要走了 下班再见...
不 不 不! 啊...
没人能诊断出我怎么了
你看 你的衬衫领口有空隙 说明你在丧失体重 你在脸红
那是发烧 而且你喘不过气
最后 你脸上有卡波西肉瘤(KS)病灶
说明你患有HIV 你正发展成晚期AIDS
你生病是因为我们的免疫系统被入侵了 而且有人对你擤鼻涕
我现在可以走了吗?
好强啊 但我的免疫系统很好
你的集中营体形师有问题 去重做你的T细胞计量
我已经做过了
他们查了T细胞淋巴瘤?
阴性的
这些都会吸引一个HIV专家的
现在松开我的拐杖 不然它就是你的新男朋友
亲爱的 如果你看看我的档案 我就嫁给你
国会说你不行 所以...
我没碰他
他这是过敏性休克
2x07 - Hunting
- 去见Stacy. - 我们给他用了肾上腺素 他好了
你需要一个律师 去见Stacy
你打了个病人
4个字 两个错误
他不是病人 而且我没打他
当然你没有 去见Stacy
不是我造成的过敏反应
可能是他的某种HIV药abacavir
我会告诉急诊室医生让他们停药的
去见Stacy
你必须治好他
以医学的标准来说这只是小菜一碟
AIDS加感染
你不治他 他会指控你人身攻击
只是他说我打他并不说明这是真的
看 我正被裸体的啦啦队长们包围着
明白了?
虽然我喜欢今早的某些行动
我忘了 周三 狂欢夜 这个可以等等!
你让我来你家见你
你老公碰巧不在
Mark去理疗了
我在等灭鼠公司
昨晚看见一只老鼠
我很惊讶你居然还敢站在地上
我几乎没睡
Mark去干吗了?
我想想 快速攀登Gregory峰而你在一次猎海豹中一直打瞌睡 (本句翻译有疑点)
打扑克 尖叫
你在干什么?
抱歉 我快疯了
你讨厌洗盘子
人是会变得
我能让你夜里睡的像个宝宝
我宁愿自己来
I'd rather take care of it myself.
我说的是老鼠
I was referring to the rat.
Trenton Pests会派一个家伙过来
Trenton Pest is sending a guy.
怎么了?
What's going on?
不是你想的那样
It's not what you think.
我知道这看上去像我们俩在洗盘子 实际上 我们是在做爱
I know it looks like we're cleaning dishes,
but actually, we're having sex.
我们在工作
We're working.
我好想自己也是个医生
Wow, wish I'd become a doctor.
这地方还真干净
Place'd be spotless.
花十分钟 把这个家伙治好 不要叫唤了
Take ten minutes, cure the guy,
and stop whining.
新病人Kalvin Ryan
I give you Kalvin Ryan.
人很浮夸 档案很无聊
So flamboyant in person, so boring on paper.
很明显是机会性感染 可能是肺结核(TB)或者囊虫性肺炎(PCP)
Obviously got an opportunistic infection,
probably TB or PCP.
你看了他的病历了吗?
Have you read his file?
我看了两眼 忽然发现那些文字没什么深度
I started, but I found the characters
two-dimensional.
他上个星期去了个HIV门诊
He went to an HIV clinic last week.
检查排除了肺结核 囊虫性肺炎(PCP) 鸟型分支杆菌群感染(MAC) 细胞巨化病毒(CMV) 单纯疱疹病毒(HSV)
Tested negative for TB, PCP, MAC, CMV, HSV.
不是感染
It's not an infection.
HIV门诊 就几个病人 赚那么多钱 重做检查
HIV clinic, so few patients, so much money.
结果都讲的通
Redo the tests.
The results make sense.
Kalvin的T细胞水平有200 足够对付感染的了
Kalvin's T-cells are at 200.
That's strong enough to fight infection.
好吧 寄生虫
Fine, parasite.
不是 粪便检验是阴性的
Nope, stool sample was negative.
两个月前 他的T细胞降到30 然后他改吃别的药
Two months ago he was down to 30 T-cells.
他的免疫系统反弹了 他的病毒拷贝数降低了 (病毒拷贝数 衡量HIV病毒数量的标准)
Then he changed his meds, his immune system rebounds,
his viral load drops.
所有指标都在恢复正常 他的病情却越来越严重
Everything's getting better, but he's getting sicker.
直面现实吧  这个病例挺有趣
Face it, this might be an interesting case.
有没有可能是他的免疫系统太强了
What if his immune system is too strong?
自体免疫性疾病 和HIV一起 不可能
And autoimmune disease? With HIV, that's impossible.
他的新HIV药物 唤醒了他原本沉睡的免疫系统
His new HIV meds kicked his system
out of a sound sleep.
苏醒后饥饿 暴躁 到处找事
Wakes up hungry, cranky, spoiling for a fight.
如果找不到主动感染源
When it doesn't find an active infection,
它就要开始攻击曾经的感染遗留下来的无害残余
it starts attacking the harmless remnants
of old infections.
免疫重建综合症
Immune Reconstitution Syndrome.
他的药物让他的病情过于好转 搞得他病了
His meds made him so much better,
he made himself sick.
- 听来很... - 无聊!
Sounds pretty--
Boring!
真的很无聊
This is so not interesting.
X光胸透寻找可能的旧感染 给他用类固醇
Chest x-ray to find the old infections.
Start him on steroids.
如果你错了 类固醇就会把他的免疫系统毁了的 病情会加重的
If you're wrong, steroids will tank
his immune system.
那样才有意思
He'll get worse.
Now that would be interesting.
可密定(抗凝血剂)在哪里?
Where's theCoumadinCoumandin?
如果你的病人血液有问题 那血液稀释剂就不是...
If your patient's got a blood problem,
then blood thinner's aren't exactly...
是给Stacy的老鼠用的 得血栓病死的
It's for Stacey's rat.
Death by anticoagulation.
靠杀一只动物来赢回Stacy...
Trying to win Stacy back by killing an animal.
太原始人了
Very caveman.
我不想要她回来
I don't want her back.
我只是想让她承认对我的感觉
I just want her to admit her feelings for me.
我去找Cuddy Cuddy炒了她或者给她换岗 我都会高兴
I go to Cuddy.
Cuddy fires her or reassigns her.
Either way, I'm happy.
如果你想她回来 要么你告诉她... 要么 更好的办法 闭嘴...
If you want her back,
either tell her...
Or better yet, shut up...
然后像其他人一样哭到睡着
and cry yourself to sleep like everybody else.
嗨 我是Mark Warner Spring大街1724号
Hi, this is Mark Warner.
1724 Spring Street.
听着 你们不需要派那个人来了 我们抓住他了(老鼠)
Uh, listen, you don't need to send that guy down.
We caught him.
不 你应该把帐单送到普林斯顿Plainsboro医院
No, you should send the bill
to Princeton Plainsboro Hospital.
James Wilson医生收
Attention Dr. James Wilson. Yeah.
对
你的淋巴结没有肿胀 好事
Your lymph nodes aren't swollen, that's good.
也许Chase医生应该检查一下
Maybe Dr. Chase should check.
抱歉 抽不出手来
Sorry, my hand's full.
他太帅了 没有安全感 你做过模特吗?
He's too pretty to be straight.
You ever done any modeling?
难道有人整天想着做模特吗?
Does anyone actually fall for that line?
每天都有 你想我为什么会成为一个摄影师?
Every day.
Why do you think I became a photographer?
我在想你们这些家伙 在上班的时候没有考虑过约会的事
I'm guessing you guys didn't think about dating
on career day.
- 我喜欢我的工作 - 真的?
I love my job.
Really?
你看上去像那种 “发现做医生能给自己异常的满足”的类型
You seem more the
"find it exceptionally satisfying" type.
我不确定这有什么区别
I'm not sure there's a difference.
你妈妈是因为糖尿病死的 你爸爸的身体怎么样?
Your mom died of diabetes.
最后一次听说 他得了肝硬化
How's your dad's health?
Last I heard, he had cirrhosis.
喜欢就是喜欢 满足感是社会认定 娱乐可以等待
Love is love.
Satisfying is social validation.
Fun can wait.
我喜欢这个
I have fun.
对 她已经订好2月的计划了
Yeah, she's got some scheduled for February.
你上一次听到你爸爸的事?
Last you heard of your father?
我16岁被他赶出家门
He threw me out when I was 16.
也就是那一次 我当时过生日不想再要玩具枪了 想出去来顿烧烤
It's just as well.
I got tired of getting BB guns for my birthday
when I'd asked for a Barbie.
爸爸可以成为真正的情人
Dads can be real sweethearts.
嗯 机敏 可爱
Mmm, sensitive and cute.
他很可爱
He's cute.
它跑到那个油烟机口去了
He ran into that heating vent right there.
希望Mark最后能消除怒火
Hopefully Mark's anger will go away eventually.
他没有生气 他只是不喜欢你
He's not angry, he just doesn't like you.
这儿没什么特别的
Nothing unique there.
他看上去对你也不是很狂野
Didn't seem really wild about you either.
他和我很好
He's fine with me.
他很生气 他在治疗小组里说的
He's angry. He said so in group.
他当然生气 他要做好几个月痛苦的理疗
Of course he's angry.
He's looking at months of painful physio.
他在生你的气
He's mad at you.
他不可能这样说
There's no way he said that.
不会 但却是事实
No. But it's true.
他嫉妒你可以走路
He resents you for being able to walk.
我也曾经这样
I've been there.
我嫉妒你了好长一段时间
I resented you for a hell of a long time.
过去式?
Past tense?
可能是医院打来的
Might be the hospital.
什么!?
What?
不是时候? 你在哪里?
Bad time? Where are you?
在你女朋友的家里 别管那些叫床声
(House) At your girlfriend's place.
Ignore the moaning and squeaking.
他的肺胆子太小了 不告诉我们是什么感染引发了他的免疫重建
His lungs are too scarred to tell which infection
triggered the immune reconstitution.
他吸烟吗?
He a smoker?
对 而且可能不只抽烟
(Cameron) Yes, and possibly more than cigarettes.
毒理检验证实 他曾经使用违禁药物
His tox screen came back positive
for recreational drugs.
没什么奇怪的 也不关诊断的事
(House) Not surprising, not medically relevant.
他的心脏看上去有点肥大
His heart looks a little enlarged.
典型的艾滋病药物副作用
(House) That's a typical side effect of AZT.
Kalvin近期的感染都是什么?
What were Kalvin's most recent infections?
弓形虫(Toxo) 细胞巨化病毒(CMV)和囊虫性肺炎(PCP)
Toxo, CMV, and PCP.
让我们假设就是其中一个
[whispering] Well, let's assume it's one of those.
用更昔洛韦对付细胞巨化病毒感染(CMV)...
Give me ganciclovir for CMV...
我们根本听不到你说什么 你在哪里?
We can hardly hear you. Where are you?
阁楼里 你女朋友的另外一个男朋友出现了
In a closet.
Your girlfriend's other boyfriend showed up.
更昔洛韦治疗细胞巨化病毒感染(CMV)
Ganciclovir for the CMV.
磺胺嘧啶治疗弓形虫(Toxo) Bactrim治疗囊虫性肺炎(PCP)
Sulfadiazine for the toxo.
Bactrim for PCP.
得挂了 杀戮时间
Gotta go.
It's killin' time.
你的毒理检验结果显示...
(Cameron) Your tox screen came back positive for...
甲安菲他明和摇头丸阳性
Crystal meth and ecstasy.
违禁药物是危险的 但对于HIV患者...
Recreational drugs are dangerous to begin with.
But for someone with HIV...
我没有把他们错当维生素吃
I didn't mistake them for vitamins.
我喜欢P&P
I'm a PNP boy.
狂欢作乐(Party & Play)
Party 'N' Play.
毒品和做爱
Drugs and sex.
你好像不大喜欢?
You don't approve.
Does the sex include condoms?
你用安全套吗?
If he's negative, sure.
如果我主动 当然 如果他主动...
If he's positive...
都淋湿了干嘛再穿雨衣?
why put on a raincoat if you're already wet?
你这样可能会感染肺炎 或者其他种类的HIV病毒
You could get hepatitis or another strain of HIV.
或者我会被汽车撞死
Or I could get hit by a bus.
艾滋病不再是死刑判决了
AIDS isn't a death sentence anymore.
我不想有遗憾
I don't wanna have any regrets.
你咳嗽多长时间了?
How long have you been coughing?
啊...大概一个小时
Uh, about an hour or so.
深呼吸
Try to take a deep breath.
什么东西?
What is it?
我想这是血
I think it's blood.
我建议你接受暴露后治疗
?????? hylaxis.
你被传染的可能微乎其微
Your chances of conversion are slim,
不过我还是想开给你三种药
but I'd like to put you on three
anti-viral medications.
Finavir zidovudine和lamivudine (都是抗病毒药物)
Nalphenovair, Zedovudine,
and Lamivudine.
它们都有副作用 头疼 反胃 噩梦
There are side-effects.
Headache, nausea, vivid dreaming.
你要分别在6周后 3个月后 6个月后进行HIV测试...
You'll be tested for HIV at six weeks, three months,
six months...
Very interesting.
太有意思了
他咳出的血溅进了Cameron的眼睛和嘴里 这有意思?
He coughs infected blood in Cameron's eyes and mouth.
我说的是他咳嗽那部分 不是说Cameron什么什么的
That's interesting.
The coughing part, not the "in Cameron" part.
新的症状 肺部血管破裂
New symptom.
Blood vessel ruptured in his lung.
我已经止住血了
I closed the tear.
这样一来就把免疫重建给排除了
Well, it takes immune reconstitution
off the table.
那把什么给展示出来了呢?
What's it put on the table?
好了 她又不在 你们不用扮演好孩子了
It's okay, she's not here.
You can skip the nice guy acts.
你要知道 人类是有感情的动物
You know, some human beings
are actually capable of human feelings.
我关不关心她也不会改变未来要发生的事
My giving a damn or not is not gonna
change what happened.
可能是卡波西肉瘤(KS)
Could be Goodpasture's syndrome.
没有水肿 没有血尿
No edema. No bloody urine.
脸上有卡波西肉瘤(KS) 那肺里也有可能有 病灶处出血
KS on his face could mean KS in his lungs
那我在修复他肺部的破裂时应该能看到的
with bleeding from the lesions.
I would have seen them when I repaired
the tear in his lung.
Wegener肉芽肿?
Wegener's granulomatosis?
那就会对类固醇类药物产生反应了
Wegener's would have responded to steroids.
你应该回家去休息一下
Maybe you should go home, take the rest of the day.
我没事
I'm fine.
哦 真不错 他假装关心 你假装不在意
Oh, this is good.
He's pretending to care, you're pretending not to.
我想我们应该重新考虑毒品的问题 Kalvin用过甲安非他明结晶
I think we should reconsider drugs.
Kalvin uses crystal meth.
因为关心自己的健康跟踪我
Concerned enough about his health to stalk me,
同时用着这些致命的药
while indulging in deadly street drugs.
可以写一篇矛盾论的论文了
A study in contradictions.
很有趣 但是医学上还是不相关
Interesting, still not medically relevant.
有可能是他的药物被污染了
It could be if his drugs were tainted.
他们用电池酸液 碱和燃油制造毒品...
They cook meth with battery acid,
lye, lantern fuel.
找到Kalvin的药 查查有没有毒
Find Kalvin's pills, test for toxins.
Foreman, you're with me.
Foreman 你跟我来
我还有个病例 需要会诊
I need a consult on another case.
我们还有病例?
We have another case?
私下的交易
It's a hip-pocket deal.
病人送来时处于一种奇特的抬颈状态
Patient presents with a distinct neck tilt.
斜颈 他是个运动员?
Wry neck. Is he an athlete?
他是个赛跑选手
He's a regular runner.
运动时有没有痛感
Any pain associated with movement?
他没提到过
None that he's complained of.
最好的可能性 耳部或肺部的感染
Best case scenario,
an infection in the ear or lungs.
最坏的 脑干肿瘤
Worst case, brain stem tumor.
应该做核磁共振 CT扫描 全套的检查手段
Should do an MRI, CAT scan, full workup.
嗯...我不这么想
Uh, I don't think so. No insurance.
病人没有保险
这里没有毒品 我去查查浴室
No drugs in here.
I'll take the bathroom.
下班后去喝一杯如何? 不要想已经发生的事了
How about a drink after work?
Take your mind off what happened.
Cameron?
我可能感染了HIV 喝一次酒不会把它冲走的
I might have HIV.
A drink's not gonna wash it away.
你被感染的机会基本上是零
There's, like, zero chance of you
contracting the virus.
"基本上是零" 和 "零" 之间有很大区别
Big difference between like zero and zero.
感染控制中心的家伙是怎么给你说的?
What did the infection control guy tell you?
那个人还算不错 一直在提醒我医院会报销我所有的费用
He was very reassuring.
Kept reminding me that the hospital
covers all my medical costs.
不过很明显他忘了告诉我 如果我的结果是阳性
Apparently forgot to mention that if I do test positive,
他们就会移交给法律部处理 法律部会想方设法挖掘我所有的污点 用来证明我...
that they'll pass it on to legal.
And legal will dig up any dirt they can
trying to prove that I'm a...
吸毒或者行为不检 所以我感染了HIV
drug user or a tramp and that's why I have HIV.
他们什么也找不到的 是不是?
It's not like they're gonna find anything, right?
Right.
对
Check this out.
看看这个
Kalvin's a photographer.
Kalvin是一个摄影师 这些坏了的东西都是些小道具
The broken bulbs were props.
玻璃是30年代的荧光玻璃
The glass is from 1930s fluorescents.
有些东西上还盖了日期邮戳
Some of the bulbs are date-stamped.
二次大战前荧光制品含有大量的铍元素
Pre-World War II, fluorescent bulbs contained
铍元素的粉末损坏肺部 使肺硬化 病人不能呼吸
large amounts of beryllium.
Beryllium dust inflames the lungs,
they get rigid, patient can't breathe.
我爸爸曾经和人合写过一篇关于急性铍中毒的论文
My father co-authored a paper
on acute berylliosis.
唉! 有一瞬间我还以为你很聪明呢
Phew!
For a moment there, I thought you were smart.
Cameron 给Kalvin的肺做活检
Cameron, get a biopsy of Kalvin's lung tissue.
用光谱仪分析一下
Run a spectrographic analysis.
我可以做
I can handle it.
没必要让整个团队冒险
No reason to risk exposing the entire team.
我到时折磨谁去?
Then who would I torment?
抱歉
I'm sorry... about what happened.
对于刚发生的一切
It's best not to talk.
最好不要说话
You'll feel a sharp pinch.
你会感到剧烈的阵痛
这实际上就是抓取一部分你的肺部组织
This actually is gonna grab a piece of your lung.
你们在我的房间里找什么?
What were you guys looking for at my hotel?
你的药 我们认为你可能吃了有毒的药
Your drugs.
Thought maybe you'd used toxic meth.
几个小时后我们就会知道你是不是铍中毒
We'll know if you were exposed to beryllium
in a few hours.
如果你们还是很好奇 ... 就在那边的椅子上我的包里
Well, if you're still curious,
it's in my bag over there on the chair.
你把毒品带进医院?!
You brought drugs into the hospital?
白跑到你房间里找了一通
Glad I wasted my time at your hotel.
我告诉你了我用过的 你又没问我要
I told you I used.
You didn't ask me for a sample.
你不是因为这件事生气 你生气是因为我把血咳到你脸上了
You're not pissed about this.
You're mad because I coughed blood on you.
那只是个意外
That was an accident.
能不能不要装好人了 没用的 更糟的是 很无聊的
Stop being nice, it's useless.
And worse, it's boring.
生气吧! 我蠢了一次 结果染上HIV
Get angry.
I had one stupid night.
你知不知道我有多生气?
I end up with HIV.
Do you have any idea how pissed-off I was?
这不是你的错
This wasn't your fault.
You broke into my house?
你破门进来的?
没办法 Mark不在家
Well, I had to. Mark isn't here.
他去理疗了
He has physio.
噢 真的? 他怎么样了?
Oh, really? How's he doing?
这些奶酪是怎么回事?
What happened with all the cheese?
Steve McQueen吃掉可嘧啶之前必须把它们藏起来
Well, I had to get rid of it before Steve McQueen
ate any Coumadin.
我给你的老鼠起的名字
I named your rat.
Steve's tilting his head.
Steve的脑袋歪了
随便哪个神经科医生都会告诉你 这是感染或者脑干肿瘤
Any neurologist will tell you
that suggests an infection or a brain stem tumor.
死了就不用担心了
Death cures both those things.
我们不能杀了他
Oh, we can't kill him.
如果是感染 可能是你屋里的某样东西引起的
If it's an infection,
it could be caused by something in your house.
也有可能影响你们
Something that could affect you guys.
闻一闻
Smell this.
- 像不像尿? - 恶!
Does it smell like urine?
Oh!
你丢了芦笋吗?
You missing any asparagus?
好了 把这个塞满 如果他没有好转 那就是肿瘤
Okay, stuff these.
If he doesn't get better, then it's a tumor.
然后呢? 化疗?
Then what, chemo?
秃头的Steve McQueen?
Steve McQueen without hair?
它会宁可英年早逝的
It's a blessing he died young.
你好
Hello.
嗨 亲爱的 抱歉我错过你了 对 我回家了
Oh, hi, honey.
I'm sorry I missed you. Yeah.
好 几分钟后见
I came home.
All right, I'll see you in a few minutes.
好 再见
Okay. Bye, hon.
胸部很疼!
Chest hurts.
心律100并且还在攀升 可能是过敏反应
Heart rate's 100 and climbing.
Could be an allergic reaction.
颈部动脉鼓胀 肯定是心包膜积水
Neck veins are up.
Must be pericardial effusion.
没有呼吸音
No wheezing.
他肺部的破裂肯定又开了
The tear in his lungs must have re-opened.
Kalvin 你的心脏周围在充血
Kalvin, you're bleeding into the area around your heart.
我要死了? 我不能呼吸!
I'm dying. I can't breathe.
血液在冲击你的心脏 等我们把血液转移走 你就会没事了
The blood's crushing your heart.
Once we remove it, you'll be fine.
如果我死了 请告诉我爸爸...
If I die, please tell my dad...
你不会死
You're not going to die.
...告诉...他...对不起
Tell him sorry.
血呢?
Where's the blood?
没有血
It's clear.
只剩下一种可能
??????
心脏里有肿瘤
?????
CT扫描证明Kalvin的心脏里有异常物质 肺中也有几个小的
and several smaller ones in his lungs.
那就是为什么他的心脏肥大了 不是艾滋病药物
That's why his heart's enlarged.
你没事吧?
Not the AZT.
You okay?
她没事 可能已经开始厌烦这个问题了
(House) She's fine.
Probably getting bored with the question.
心脏和肺部的异常物质 可能是是什么癌症?
Masses in the heart and lungs.
kind of cancer are we looking at?
不一定就是癌症
They may not be cacancerous.
这是典型的非霍奇金症淋巴癌
This is classic non-Hodgkins lymphoma.
HIV阳性的病人外加心脏中有异常物质
HIV positive patient with a primary heart mass?
可能是肉状瘤
It could be sarcoidosis.
肺部活检显示正常
His lung tissue is negative.
淋巴瘤就是死刑 肉状瘤可以治愈的
Lymphoma's a death sentence, sarcoidosis is treatable.
那耳朵也应该有感染 但那个也不是阳性...
So's an ear infection.
Since he didn't test positive for that either.
我想做一下Kveim-siltzbach测试
I wanna do the Kveim Siltzbach test.
你知道那样的话Cuddy要签多少份文件吗?
Do you have any idea how much paperwork
Cuddy's gonna need signed?
去做吧
Do it.
对了...
So...
病人的爸爸是怎么回事?
how is the patient's father?
嗯...
"Tell my dad I'm sorry."
告诉我爸爸我对不起他?
可能当年把老爷子给惹毛了
Might as well have waved a red flag at a bull.
他不会来的
He's not coming.
还好不算是悲剧
Well, it's not a tragedy.
爸爸不想见他 他也不想见爸爸
Dad doesn't wanna see him, he doesn't wanna see the dad.
你是唯一一个希望他们见面的
You're the only one who wants them together.
- 他说的! - 他认为自己要死了
He asked--
人之将死 一样说谎 (老黑的翻译 一字不改放上来)
He thought he was dying. Dying people lie too.
希望他们工作少点 希望他们人变好些 希望他们为小猫们开孤儿院
Wished they'd worked less.
They'd been nicer.
They'd opened orphanages for kittens.
如果你真的想做些什么 做吧 别存着了
If you really wanna do something,
you do it.
You don't save it for a sound bite.
如果你要死了 你会说什么?
What did you say when you thought you were dying?
另一方面讲
On the other hand...
他爸爸抛弃了他
His dad tossed him out.
他为什么要道歉呢?
So what's our guy want to apologize for?
每个人都有遗憾
Everybody has regrets.
如果你心脏和肺部的组织是肉状瘤
If the growths in your lungs and heart are sarcoid,
你的身体就会认出这个
your body will recognize this material.
我们会在你的胳膊上看到反应
And we'll see a reaction on your arm.
你真的想见你的爸爸?
Did you really want to see your dad?
你给他打电话了?
You called him?
谢谢
Thanks.
他会来 试着让我变好
He would've come and tried to straighten me out.
你怎么样了?
How are you holding up?
- 我很好 - 真可信
I'm fine.
Convincing.
我的药你们怎么处理了?
What'd you do with my drugs?
实验室分析完了就扔掉了
The lab disposes of them after analysis.
可惜
Too bad.
也许对你有点用呢
They could have done you some good.
我可不喜欢那个
They're not really my thing.
你要知道 我不希望你吃那个玩意儿 但...
You know, I hope you don't have it.
但是感染HIV病毒可能是发生在我身上的最好的事了
But getting HIV might have been
the best thing that ever happened to me.
我曾经是个好孩子
I used to be a good boy.
从不想惹别人生气...
Never wanted to piss anybody off.
遵纪守法 助人为乐
Playing by the rules makes everybody else happy.
现在 我很快乐
Now I'm happy.
就是说只有他做理疗的时候 你才会出现?
So you just show up every time he's at physio?
当然不是! 他去集体治疗小组 或者和朋友出去吃饭的时候也去
Of course not.
Also when he's at group therapy
or out for dinner with friends.
当她没注意向Mark提到 你来过...?
And when she happens to mention to Mark
that you dropped by...
你把什么都告诉你老婆?
You tell your wife everything?
这是个...过程
It's a...process.
但是Stacy没有什么理由向Mark隐瞒这个
But Stacy doesn't have any reason
to hide this from Mark.
据她现在所知 Mark对你的出现还算可以忍受
As far as she knows,
我打赌她尽可能不向Mark提到我
Mark's okay with you being there.
My bet is she mentions me to Mark
因为她认为Mark认为她对我还有感觉
as little as possible.
She thinks that he thinks that she still
你知道她为什么这么想吗?
has feelings for me.
And you know why she thinks that?
因为她对你还有感觉?
Because she still has feelings for you?
如果你说的没错 她确实告诉他了 我想今晚我就会进不去门
If you're right, she did tell him,
and I don't get through the door tonight.
如果我说对了...
If I'm right...
我们要在这里呆多长时间?
So how long do we stay here?
直到有什么事发生
Until something happens.
他不会出来陪我们了
He's not gonna come out with us right here.
我们在下风处 而他看上去有点听力衰弱
We are downwind, and he seems to have
a hearing loss.
他又不瞎
He's not blind.
Steve McQueen不会逃避危险
Steve McQueen does not run from danger.
抗生素 从另一方面讲...
Antibiotics, on the other hand...
他在咬药片周围? 真聪明!
He ate around the pill?
承认吧 你喜欢他
Smart.
Admit it, you like him.
他很好...作为一个老鼠来说
He's all right. For a rat.
你想知道他有多酷吗?
You wanna know how cool he is?
他的尿液显示身体内有氰化氢 甲醛 铅
His urine showed traces of hydrogen cyanide,
formaldehyde, lead.
他抽烟
He's a smoker.
你老公开始抽烟...
Your husband's been lighting up.
很愚蠢的想法 会导致他的AIP...
Which is particularly stupid, given that it could
好了 我把我的烟灰倒通风孔里了 Mark就不会知道了
'cause his AIP to--
Okay, I blow my smoke into the vent
so Mark doesn't know.
我一直知道
I always knew.
吹牛!
You're bluffing.
我手术后两个星期你开始的
You started two weeks after my surgery.
先是薄荷醇 一个月后开始抽烟了
Menthols...
你当时怎么不说啊?
then lights after a month.
Why didn't you say anything?
因为它可以帮助我监控你的痛苦水平
'Cause it helped me monitor your misery level.
一天一次很舒服 多于六次 你就是在地狱里了
One trip outside was a good day.
Upwards of six, you were in hell.
你应该问我过怎么样的!
You could have asked me how I was.
I already knew.
我已经知道了
I'm sorry you were miserable.
抱歉让你很痛苦
抱歉让你这么痛苦
Sorry I caused you so much pain.
啊哈
很高兴你改主意了
Thought you'd change your mind about that drink.
请进
Come on in.
你应该有改变的 校园里有个新地方...
You should get changed.
There's this new place on campus that looks--
- 你很high? - 嗯
Are you high?
我以为你把药都扔掉了
I thought the lab disposed of the drugs.
不是全部
Not all of it.
呃 等等...
Uh, slow down.
你的瞳孔在扩大!
Your pupils are dilated. You're not...
好了 Chase 别把我变成那个好孩子
Come on, Chase, don't turn into
a good guy on me now.
你迟到了 而且宿醉
You're late.
And hung over.
也许不是
Or maybe not.
你干嘛拿着一只老鼠?
Why do you have a rat?
嫉妒吗?
Jealous?
出去! 你怎么能这么对我!
(Kalvin) Out of my room!
(Michael) Don't you dare put this on me!
我不会求你的 爸爸!
(Kalvin) I'm not gonna grovel, Dad.
我要的不是这个的
That's not what I'm asking for.
谁他妈信! 你说过没有打电话!
(Kalvin) Like hell it isn't.
You said you didn't call.
不用管我 我是来看戏的
Don't mind me.
随便 这里没什么好看的
Just here for the show.
Well, there's not gonna be any.
伟大的道歉怎么没了? 昨天 他还说 "爸爸 对不起"
What happened to the big apology?
Yesterday, he was all,
"Daddy, I'm so sowwy."
这不关你的事
This is none of your business.
你跟踪我之前就应该想到的
You should have thought of that
before you stalked me.
现在我忽然有兴趣了
Now I'm interested.
他要为什么道歉? 是你把他踢出家门的
So what's he got to apologize for?
我为什么要那样做?
You're the one who tossed him out.
不知道 因为你很难向你的打猎的伙伴们吹嘘
Now, why would I do that?
I don't know,
说你的儿子没完没了的咳嗽
'cause it's tough to brag to your hunting buddies
that your son knows all the words to The Wiz.
假话!
That's a lie.
42街?
42nd Street.
喝多了然后打他 太容易了 可以解释他为什么恨你
Much easier just to get drunk and beat him.
也可以解释你的肝硬化
Explains his hating you.
也可以解释为什么我说的越多 你出汗越多
Also your cirrhosis.
Also why the more I talk, the more you sweat.
它不能解释的是... 为什么他要向你道歉
What it doesn't explain...
is why he's gotta apologize to you.
你对自己的同性恋行为 还有点愧疚之心?
Residual guilt for sharing
your special toy with other boys?
不要胡说
Just leave it alone.
还是说你想这个老顽固在你死后内心能平静一点?
You just wanna leave the bigot
听着 这个事和他搞同性恋没有一丁点的关系!
with some peace of mind after you're gone?
Look, this has got nothing, and I mean nothing,
to do with him being gay.
Kal他自作自受 还害了他妈妈!
Kal brought this on himself
with what he did to his mother.
他偷了她用来炫耀的衣服?
He steal her signature look?
不是 他杀了她
No
??
Kalvin在撒谎!
Kalvin lied.
对 当然让人震惊
Yeah, that certainly is shocking.
妈妈的肾脏衰竭了 她需要移植一个 他们检查了Kalvin 配型成功
Mom's kidneys were failing,
she needed a transplant.
他同时也是HIV阳性 妈妈再也没找到合适的捐赠人 她死了
They tested Kalvin, he was a match.
He was also positive for HIV.
Mom never found a qualified donor.
She dies.
悲剧
(House) Tragic tale.
穿这么紧身 说话速度这么快 不停地来回移动
Undercut slightly by the rapid-fire delivery
今天早晨咖啡喝多了?
and constant movement.
他没有杀她 我们身体并不是给父母提供器官的农场
Too much coffee this morning?
He didn't kill her.
这不是80年代 我们都知道HIV是怎么传染的!
Our bodies aren't donor farms for our parents.
It's not 1980.
We know how HIV is transmitted.
如果Kalvin因为无保护性交 导致感染HIV 爸爸有理由发怒!
If Kalvin got HIV through unprotected sex,
你一直用安全套吗?
Dad has every right to be pissed.
呃... 当然!
So you always use a condom?
社会下层的兄弟 没办法
Uh, yeah.
嗯 还没准备好要个小Foreman
Brothers on the down-low got to.
你?
Not ready for any Foreman Juniors yet.
工作的女孩都很顽固
You?
Working girls are sticklers.
你不准备找Chase的碴?
You're not gonna poll Chase?
我不是白痴
I'm not an idiot.
你当然不是
Obviously not.
如果有机会 谁不会去和一个 吃了药的同事睡觉?
Who doesn't sleep with a drugged-out colleague
when they have a chance?
Wilson在哪里?
Where's Wilson?
我们有了病人Kveim检查的结果
We got the results of the Kveim test.
所以... 我得了癌症?
So, I have cancer?
最大的可能性 是的
In all likelihood, yeah.
非霍奇金淋巴瘤
Non-Hodgkins lymphoma.
所以我...要死了?
And I am...dying.
我们需要肿瘤的活体进行检验 它在你的主动脉附近 所以...
We need to biopsy the tumor.
做这个活体取样危险性非常大
It's near your aorta, so getting that sample
我爸爸还在这里吗?
carries serious risks.
Is my dad still here?
他没进来?
He hasn't been in?
我们会把你心脏附近的组织染色 让肿瘤在CT上显形
We'll inject the dye
around your heart to make the tumor visible
然后会做一个小手术 植入一根引线通到心脏中
on the CT.
Then a surgeon inserts a guidewire,
然后截取一点肿瘤的组织 以便我们用显微镜观察
runs it up into your heart,
where he takes a small piece of that tumor
so we can look at it under the microscope.
阿提凡 帮你镇定一下 (镇静剂 不是阿凡提)
Atavan.
你怎么这么镇定?
It'll help settle you down.
药效还没过去呢
Why are you so calm?
Not coming off meth helps.
昨晚的事也许不该再发生了
Last night probably shouldn't happen again.
你以为我想吗?
Do you think I want it to?
两个人发生了关系 除非情况很糟糕
When two people have had sex,
如果他们能再做 他们还会再做
unless it sucks,
if they can do it again, they're gonna do it again.
然后事情就复杂了
And that's when things get complicated.
昨晚还算不错
And it didn't suck.
你现在又找了个借口 去找你的老情人叙旧
So now you've gotta drum up another excuse
to be around the love of your life.
再打一个病人
Could hit another patient.
不是 不想重复自己 人们会认为我很刻板
Nah, don't like to repeat myself.
看样子你不会再让老鼠跑掉 然后你再抓回来了
People will say I'm formulaic.
Well that rules out letting the rat go
我不能那样做
so you can catch him again.
Steve 需要两个星期的抗生素 和一个无烟的环境
I can't do that.
Steve needs two weeks antibiotics
烟草会加剧他的感染
and a smoke free environment.
老鼠真的病了?
Cigarettes aggravated his infection.
那个东西会传染整个医院的!
The rat is actually sick?
Steve的感染不会传染人类
That thing could infect the entire hospital.
Steve's infection is not contagious to humans.
我是个白痴 我怎么忘了支原体感染? 那个是病人的父亲?
I'm an idiot. How do I miss mycoplasmosis?
对 你记得黑死病吗? 就是从老鼠开始的
Was that the kid's father?
Yeah.
他在走廊里干什么? 那个孩子的活检准备好了吗?
Remember the black death? Started with rats.
Well, what's he doing in the hallway?
他只是不想进病房
Is the kid getting his biopsy already?
谁知道还有没有什么别的原因? 寄生虫? 细菌感染?
He just won't go in the room.
Who knows what else he has.
- 这孩子没有寄生虫 - 不是孩子 是老鼠
Parasites, bacterial infection?
The kid doesn't have parasites.
他还出汗吗?
Not the kid, the rat.
Was he still sweating?
老鼠只能通过尾巴流汗
Rats only sweat through their tails.
不是老鼠 是爸爸!
Not the rat, the dad.
他们从哪儿来的?
Where are they from?
呃...蒙大拿 怎么了? (蒙大拿 美国打猎胜地)
Uh, Montana. What's going on?
你是对的 就是寄生虫
You were right, it's a parasite.
取消活检 会杀了他的
Cancel the biopsy, it'll kill him.
嘿 老爹 跟我来!
Hey, daddy, come with me.
好 啊... 我不去那里
Yeah, uh, I'm not going in there.
你儿子要和你说话
Your son asked to talk to you.
他来这里干什么?
Why is he here?
他想和你说话
He wanted to talk to you.
啊哈
Oh.
你们两个曾经一起打猎?
Did you two used to hunt together?
狐狸 你们杀过狐狸吗?
Foxes. Did you kill foxes?
蒙大拿州啊
It's Montana.
你胸部的组织不是肿瘤
Those masses in your chest are not tumors.
他们是寄生虫囊肿 这个虫子叫棘球绦虫
They're parasitic cysts from a bug called
你们碰过死狐狸 它们登陆你们的身体 它们可以潜伏几十年
echinococcosis.
Touch a dead fox, they jump aboard,
- 生长 繁殖 购物 化装演出
they can hunker down for decades.
Growing, spawning, shopping.
我查过寄生虫了
Putting on plays.
I've been tested for parasites.
好吧 是癌症 高兴了?
Okay, it's cancer.
囊肿隔离了寄生虫
You happy?
The cysts isolate the parasites.
粪便检验的时候就查不来 甚至血检 心脏...
Keep them from showing up in stool samples.
好了 你根本不需要我
Even a blood test, cardiac--
但你的肝里也有同样的东西
All right, you don't need me for this.
But you've got the same things in your liver.
我有肝硬化
I have cirrhosis.
肝脏囊肿的症状和它一样 不过还多一个 发烧
Liver cysts have identical symptoms.
肝脏囊肿我们可以查出来的
With one addition, fever.
And liver cysts we can test for.
你的诊断结果可以确诊Kalvin的
Your diagnosis could confirm Kalvin's.
那么 选项A 我们抽点血...
So, option A-- we draw some blood--
不 不 听着 不要碰我
No, no, look, you're not touching me.
看到没 这就是为什么我找你来
See, this is why I need you here.
我想让你告诉你儿子 你不想做个简单而无痛的血检来救他的命
I want you to tell your son
that you won't take a simple
painless blood test to save his life.
你从来没有对你妈妈的事表示过一点遗憾
You never expressed a shred of regret
天哪 爸爸...
for what happened to your mother.
如果你带了那该死的安全套 你就会没事
Jeez, Dad.
If you'd have worn a damn rubber,
你就能救她的命 你就不会躺在这里!
you'd have been fine.
You could have saved her life.
You wouldn't be lying here.
好好 好好 我知道了!
(House) Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I get it.
他在毁灭自己也在毁灭你爱的东西 你对此非常非常生气
You're really mad at him for killing himself
我没有时间搞这个 你要道歉吗?
and for destroying everything you love.
I don't have time for this.
我在用我想的方式生活
Are you gonna apologize?
你给我点血吗?
I'm living my life the way I want.
如果他不在乎 我也不!
Are you gonna give me some blood?
Look, if he doesn't give a damn,
好 B选项
then neither do I.
Okay, option B.
为什么你的妻子要自杀? 她恨你吗?
Why did your wife kill herself?
她有糖尿病!
Did she hate you?
你一点也不了解我的Susan
She was a diabetic.
要么Susan想死 要么她又肥又蠢
You know, you don't know a thing about my Susan.
Either Susan wanted to die,
吃高糖饼干来代替枪
or she was both fat and stupid.
能吃的女人 她们永远没有吃饱的时候!
Used a Twinkie instead of a gun.
And girls with big appetites,
闭嘴!
well, they just can't get enough of anything.
也许尝过这个国家的每种饼干!
Shut up.
闭嘴!
Probably nibbled on every Devil Dog in the county.
如果我没说清楚 我不是说那些美味的小吃...
Shut up! Jeez, I'm not making myself clear.
你这个婊子养的!
I don't mean the delicious snack.
You son of a bitch!
啊? 来啊!
Yeah?
谢谢你 这代表我可以这样做了
Come on!
Thank you. That means I can do this.
我们需要些肾上腺素 快!
We're gonna need some epi in here, stat!
你疯了吗?!
Are you out of your mind?
你说了你不介意
You said you didn't care.
注意到没有你是为什么不能呼吸的?
Notice how you can't breathe?
要么是我的拐杖
Now either that's the cane,
要么就是我刚弄破了一个我们刚刚在讨论的包囊
or I just ruptured one of those liver cysts
你正在经历过敏性休克
we were chatting about.
和你儿子意外撞到我朋友的车后 的症状一模一样
And you've gone into anaphylactic shock.
Exactly the same when your son did when he accidentally
我太兴奋了 没有判断能力了!
tripped against my friend's car.
I['m just so excited to find out which.
我去安排手术
I'll go schedule the surgery.
夹子
Clamp.
血压稳定
Pressure's holding.
两个成功的手术 两条人命
Two successful surgeries, two lives saved.
超出定量了 下个星期能不能放我假?
I'm over my quota.
Can I have next week off?
攻击两个家庭成员
Two family members assaulted.
- 正当防卫 - 你引诱他下手
[scoffs] It was self-defense.
你说的对 我活该
You baited him.
You're right, I was asking for it.
低胸衬衫 写着“干我”之类的胸部
The low-cut blouse, the "do-me" pumps.
你利用寄生虫让他的内脏出血 他可以起诉你
You flooded his gut with a parasite, he could sue.
去见Stacy
Go see Stacy.
好
Okay.
什么? 好? 没有骂人? 没有诉苦? 没有撕衣服?
That's it? "Okay"?
No name-calling, no squawking,
no rending of garments?
我喜欢这件T恤
I like this T-shirt.
你骗我
You lied to me.
如果这和我妈妈相关...
If this is about my mom--
这和你孤独悲惨的生活有关
This is about your lonely, miserable life.
我不悲惨
I'm not miserable.
不论哪里 只要有同性恋酒吧 我就不孤独
And as long as there's a gay bar around, I'm never lonely.
除了你爸爸 都没人来看你
You haven't had a single visitor except for your dad.
毒品很伟大 HIV给了你自由
Drugs are great. HIV freed you.
你爸爸恨你 你这么高兴
Your dad hates you. You're so happy.
全都是谎言!
Everything's a lie.
你因为妈妈的死责怪自己
You blame yourself for your mom's death.
你不是在自娱自乐 你是在毁灭自己
You're not trying to have fun, you're trying to self-destruct.
你想自杀吗? 好 但是干脆一点!
You wanna kill yourself? Fine.
But stop recruiting.
听说你又打了一个病人
Heard you hit another patient.
嗯 对 为什么不呢?
[scoffs] Yeah, sure. Why not?
他先打我
He hit me first.
Cuddy没有和我提到这个 让我看看
Cuddy didn't mention that. Let me see.
I'm the doctor.
我是医生
我是纯粹出于法律上的关心
My concern is purely legal. Looks okay.
看着没事 疼吗?
Does it hurt?
一点
A little.
需要冷敷一下
You need some ice.
Mark不可能不知道...
There's no way that Mark doesn't know.
你抽烟的事
About the smoking.
他应该说点什么的
He would have said something.
看来他已经好几个月没碰你了
Then he hasn't been near you in months.
We're fine.
我们很好
没这么简单
Can't be easy.
别乱动
Stop squirming.
你为什么要撒谎?
Why would you lie about this?
我没在撒谎
I'm not lying.
我并不在意你是不是在和他睡觉 但如果你没有 那么...
I don't care if you're sleeping with him or not,
我有
but you're not, so--
你在说谎
I am.
You're lying.
你知道我什么时候做爱? 你连这个也能闻出来?
You know when I have sex?
You can smell that on me too?
唯一能知道我和Mark之间的事的人 就是我和Mark
The only people that know about
what's going on with me and Mark,
我了解你
are me and Mark.
I just know you.
我也了解你
And I know you.
你自信 你傲慢 但是你从来不确定除非有个理由能让你确认
You're confident, arrogant,
but you are never certain
unless there's a reason to be certain.
还有一个人知道 我告诉你了我在看Harper医生
One other person knew.
I told you I was seeing Dr. Harper.
你可以很简单的进入她的办公室 你读了我的档案
You can easily get into her office.
You read my file.
你读了我的档案?
那些盘子 关心 哦...
The dishes,
the concern, the, oh, acting like a human being.
装得像个人?
你...
You have--
一直在欺骗我?
This whole time, you've been manipulating me.
从我把洗洁精倒刷子上时你就知道我在使坏
You knew that I had an angle the moment I--
poured soap onto a scrub brush.
你应该把我扔出去的
You could've thrown me out.
或者忽略我 或者再找一个灭鼠公司
Or ignored me, or found another exterminator.
但是你没有告诉Mark我经常来
But you didn't even tell Mark that I kept coming by.
你让这些事发生 因为你想和我一起
You let this happen because you wanna be with me.
不再需要了
I don't anymore.
滚
Get out.
[Amos Lee's Colors]
* *
对不起
I'm sorry.
# Yesterday I got lost in the circus #
* Yesterday I got *
* Lost in circles *
# Feeling like such a mess #
* Feeling like such a mess *
# And now I'm down I'm just hanging on the corner #
* And now I'm down I'm just *
* Hanging on the corner *
# I can't help but reminisce #
* I can't help but reminisce *
# I know we all We all got our faults #
* I know we all *
* We all got our faults *
# We get locked in our vaults, and we stay.. #
* We get locked in our vaults *
* And we stay *
# When you're gone #
* When you're gone *
# All the colours fade When you're gone #
* All the colors fade *
* When you're gone *
# No new years day parade You're gone #
* No New Year's Day parade *
* You're gone *
# Colours seem to fade #
* Colors seem to fade *
* Yeah * *
Sync:FRM-xxy -=http://www.1000fr.com=-